Yeah.
Hello, afternoon.
Hello.
Mm.
No.
Ohh.
Hey.
Do we know if...
Jack around.
He can join whenever he cans.
Whenever you're ready, Theo.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
There was a start with...
The.
Follow-up tasks from last week,
and then I'll go into more detail.
So the yeah, I'll go over hardware,
pen and charge up and software readiness
today,
including two pen application and 360 web
app.
So yeah, when we last spoke,
we spoke about assembling,
so the verification of the plastics,
those reviews are now done.
We've got short term and long term
solutions to some, yeah.
relatively small issues that we came
across with the with the plastics,
Yeah.
but on the whole plastics are performing
performing really well from a functional
perspective and yeah cosmetic perspective.
So
Yeah,
we've kicked off the 21 build with OSI.
ready to, you know,
to give us the units to go through this
more verification,
go through pre-compliance.
We.
Have, yeah,
given the green light on charge hub
tooling, charging hub tooling, yeah,
finalising the the tolerances for
production.
They've been given go ahead and they've
given us.
Yeah,
a time frame for those units and the T
zeros.
We also specified the volume for T0 units,
so those first shots of the charger hub
that come off the tool.
We've specified that volume,
so that's all moving ahead.
We.
Yeah, we've had the M11 review.
I've conducted a structured review of.
Most of that now,
I've got a few bits and pieces that I
need to finish up.
The bulk of that is done now and in the
process of feeding that back to...
To the team.
I'll share some of that new functionality
in this course so you can see what some
of those updates look like and to you
know what they mean for our users.
Ohh.
And in terms of the packaging specs,
they progressed to about, you know,
Yeah.
30% done. But once the software reviewed,
I'll be able to focus and focus some more
time on that.
And in terms of process and ownership,
that's, yeah, very close,
close conversation with Nick and Chloe
about ownership and priorities.
Those.
Sing and.
Yeah, dig in a little bit more.
Into a bit more detail.
OK.
And.
B.
Here, we've gone through verification,
functional verification of these
enclosures, and...
There were.
There was one issue of bosses cracking,
so when you drive the screw in one or two
of the bosses were cracking,
so we've got a short-term solution to
that,
which is to bore out the bore out the box
in a down to the.
Long term solution is to is to tweak the
tooling.
So as I have been given short term
instructions and Bang and now and I had a
meeting with Bang last week and so long
term solutions which effectively just
reduce any post will remove post any post
processing that's required.
to ensure that the units,
the bosses aren't cracking,
the units going to get up with as little
hands-on time as possible, basically. So,
that was the that was the main one. Yeah,
another one.
that we had was the side buttons,
they were functioning well.
The plastic is a little bit stiffer than
the MGF.
So in terms of the three buttons on the
side here,
Okay.
this button is a little bit stiffer than
these two. So we have, yeah,
which is the power button.
So the power button is slightly stiffer
than the volume buttons, which
It.
I don't think it's going to pose a
usability issue at all. And the end,
so from a functional,
from a perception point of view,
it doesn't feel wrong because these two
feel the same.
This one feels slightly different and it
has different function.
So it's slightly stiffer.
So not too concerned about that.
This button feels very similar to these
buttons.
Um, cosmetically, um, yeah, enclosures.
Looking and feeling good.
There's a little bit of...
It's very hard to,
you have to get the pen in the right
light to be able to see it,
but there's a little bit of a difference
in surface finish along this edge here.
So I'm investigating different how we can
get that cleaned up.
But it's, yeah,
you need to get it in the right lines.
It's not a very obvious thing,
but it is something I'd like to
investigate if we can,
if we can neaten up a bit.
Micro.
So, yeah.
What's the two orange bands, Theo?
I just haven't glued this display on,
yeah, yeah, so it's masking,
Oh, fine. Okay.
They happen to look like part of the
it's masking tape.
It's.
design because they're orange.
Yeah, yeah, I know, English.
They're mandatory, Sharmella.
I have to be there.
Yeah.
They look good. It looks good, Theo.
It looks good.
Yeah.
Thanks. Yeah.
The black and white looks good.
With the orange buttons.
Mm.
Yeah.
Yeah, colour. Yeah, everything's.
Or yellow, I don't know what.
Everything's, yeah,
it's a very warm yellow,
so it's about as close to orange as you
can get for a yellow.
Okay.
Mm.
Yeah, it looks nice.
So, yeah, yeah, that's just my,
it's just 'cause I haven't glued this
Okay.
display on while some doing reviews,
but it's very thin, it's very thin.
Talk in menu on.
Yeah, and there's a little bit of a...
You try, yeah, it's difficult to see,
but there's a little bit of...
Surface finish, so.
Introduction.
Interfection on the inside of the window
here as well, which...
It kind of losing a finger.
But these are cosmetic things,
aren't they,
as opposed to functionality issues.
Yeah, yeah, exactly, yeah, so.
Is that correct?
Helps.
How pretty does it look around the camera
area?
Inside of here.
Yeah.
I'm really happy with how it looks in the
end.
Let me switch cameras so I can give you
better view.
Yeah.
We see in here.
Yeah, it looks neat, doesn't it?
Boome.
Yeah, it's going neat. Yeah,
alignment's looking good for the camera.
There's no, you know, there's no...
holes or anything, yeah. A lot of...
But what?
and you're happy with all the button
pushes that they are.
Yeah, there was.
Are they Apple quality or are they not
Apple quality? Do they feel good to push?
What do they feel? Yeah.
Yeah, they feel good to push. Yeah,
they are, yeah, yeah, they're feeling,
they're feeling tactile.
They're feeling tactile in assembly.
There is some screw I've added in an
additional assembly step.
To.
To cheque the tactile field before.
going to the next assembly step,
because you can actually adjust the
feeling slightly by talking the talking
some internal screws differently.
So in the 21 units.
But you think it feels good?
It feels good, yeah. Yeah, I can show you.
Yeah, the side buttons feel good.
And what about the side buttons?
Like I say,
this one is slightly stiffer than these.
It doesn't feel wrong because it's a
different function and power has,
you know, power is more like
definitive kind of thing,
action to take as opposed to volume and
it's, you know, it's visually separated.
There will be icons on the side here,
but they're not etched onto this unit to
distinguish the function.
And that button is just your pen or that
button is all Pens will feel different.
B.
But yeah, all Pens will feel different.
OK.
Yeah.
Yeah, so.
When we get the 20, yeah,
with the 21 build, we'll...
Understand.
Ann.
You know, within these subjective points,
we can get a bit more,
get a bit more feedback,
but how they feel.
So, yeah, I can,
I can pile this and I can show you the
buttons.
The button's working.
Firmware-wise, when it powers on,
we've reduced the frequency and, um,
and the...
Length of time that the.
Then, buzzes for,
so it feels more friendly than quite as
intense, which is nice.
You can see we've still got that initial
stretched logo that comes up.
That's the one he's removing.
but we've got a nicer transition that's
still skewed.
We do have a nicer transition.
I can show you.
Yeah,
I can show you some more developments for
software in terms of usability and then I
can come on and sort of show you some
other, you know,
hardware related functionality.
But we've got QR code login working and
we've got an updated student login code.
approach.
So I can show you that if I find myself
here.
We've got this DaVinci Code scroll wheel.
That's much better.
Yeah.
Which is?
Much more usable.
Ann.
Yeah, which is great, then if I log out.
Then I can also show you the QR.
Login.
So if I go to 360.
Generate my.
Yeah.
You can see there's a little lag between
pressing and the camera opening.
So that's the usability point I'd like to
improve because there isn't a loader for
that.
I'm just going to share screen as well
for a second here.
So I'm here in 360 and I can go to, oh,
give me a second.
So, this is where my...
Login would be.
Theo.
This is what we'd have group called group
printouts,
so you can see this PDF is generated.
This has just got me on it,
but this would have blocks for each
student.
So then I'm just going to hold up my pen.
To that QR code.
See on the camera at the moment.
There's a bit of a lag in the camera at
the moment,
which is something I'm feeding back on,
just doing this from the screen as
opposed to from a printer.
I know when I tried to do this a few
months ago,
it didn't work from the screen and I had
to print it out. Is that still the case?
I got it to work from,
I got it to work from the screen earlier.
Um...
It was in a playable, man.
Mm.
Trying.
Yeah, so I'm just gonna try this game,
so I get...
Scanning QR code.
We want we want to introduce a loader
here, so you know when.
When it's thinking about it,
opens the viewfinder,
Max.
Yeah.
so there's a bit of a lag on the
viewfinder at the moment,
something we're looking into.
Bang.
Okay,
I couldn't get that to work for some
reason; the second camera wasn't working.
A bit frustrating. I can't show you.
I got, yeah,
it was the first time I got to work just
now and obviously now I'm trying to show
people. It isn't working for me.
So just log in this way first.
I log in this way to show you the other
features.
Ann.
Yeah, so you can see.
We've got the.
Do you want to move that back onto the
main screen, Theo? I tried to spotlight,
Ohh yeah, sorry, sorry, yeah.
but it didn't work.
Claudine.
So I think the second camera opening
sometimes is causing is causing crashes.
I've just had to I've just had to restart.
Yeah,
there is a bug with memory allocation
with a second camera.
They are working on fixing until this
morning.
Yeah.
So when I just open the second camera
there and then try to log in, yeah,
Ann.
Yeah.
it's just...
It's just crashed, so I'm just restarting.
It's a known, known bug, it says.
Theo Higgins.
So, yeah,
you can see with the navigation buttons,
um, yeah, we've got...
Are they now working? That's nice.
Okay.
Those map, they just they map nicely,
you know,
we're not getting any false positives or
or like non presses.
I've just gone into read mode.
You can see we've got the scanning
illustration,
the sequential scanning illustration in
place now.
So non-text based instructions for
Nice.
scanning. Yeah,
you can see it's a little bit stretched
here.
Yeah, that's one of my...
On modes of feedback, which, yeah,
actually it just needs to be,
it's been stretched out, and you can see,
yeah, if I go back here,
I use the buttons, so, but yeah,
buttons are working for top-level menus,
they're not functional for some of the
menus at the moment.
Can you hear the,
can you hear it speaking to me? Yeah. So,
Yep.
Mm.
so the talking menu, you know,
it makes sense with the navigation
buttons and you can see those both
working together nicely. So,
I'm able to do a lot of navigation
without having to.
Basically, what happened to, you know,
really engage with the screen.
Another thing we've got functioning at
the moment, we've got functioning now is,
you know,
we've got visibility on the tools.
within that mode before you engage with
any text. So yeah,
when you enter a mode and you're looking
for a tool, so with intent,
you're able to be able to explore
Ed.
The pen and find your tool before you
actually start Scanning anything,
which is was something we didn't have we
didn't have before.
And.
Which is nice, it just gives us more.
So yeah, we've got here.
All the words I just scanned in and we've
got the GTS button here,
so I want to listen to landing.
I can press that if I want to listen to
spot. I listen to spot.
I thought you had expanded the database
to 6000 words.
Uh, 3000 at the moment,
so landing and spot on on in there.
I still not in the 1st 3000 words. Okay,
fair enough.
Yeah, uh,
we've got below is horizon in the
The.
horizon's in there.
But yeah,
we've got TGS access to each of those,
so you're able to, you know,
visually see the split with the syllables
and hear at the same time. And
What's it saying? Horizon, one word.
Yeah, it reads this word,
so it doesn't read. Yeah,
The yellow word, yeah.
it just reads as it is there.
And same for graphemes, we
We have.
Yeah, the TTS.
Functioning from this button,
I'd be able to draw to draw a comparison
between the two.
We also have.
Verizon.
We've got some nicer.
Nice icons.
In place now, so yeah,
lots of these icons have been sorted out,
so you know they were sort of stretched
stretched for access to to set text
settings in here.
We can.
Favourite words we can.
And we've also got, yeah,
second camera functionality working.
It may crash then, but I'll just,
I'll show you,
I'll show you what that's looking like.
There's no explore button.
What happened to the explore button?
I think it's I think it's only functional
in the read mode app at the in read mode
Yeah.
at the moment, which which it should,
yeah,
it should be available in all of them,
so I'll show you, yeah,
I should be able to show you explore.
from read mode shortly.
So I'm just lining up for the second
camera now.
So yeah, there's a few.
There's a few, a fair few usability.
Um...
Enhancements that are required for the
second camera.
I'm not happy with that image,
so I'm going to take it again.
It's a bit fuzzy.
Yeah.
So much you can see.
It looks, it looks a bit fuzzy.
I'm going to...
It's.
Yeah.
Okay, yes,
image is a bit fuzzy at the time.
Yeah, let me go back to read mode.
I'll show you the explore functionality
and then I'll have another go at a second
camera.
And.
Fine, got some good words in there.
Landing spot below the horizon.
Aditya.
There was no place to die to get.
The accent still sounds American.
Have we done any work with multiple
accents?
Baban.
It's pending, so it's a, yeah,
it's something,
it's something for a to have an English,
yeah, to have an English accent is.
Oh.
Yeah, part of the the pre-pilot scope,
so it's still it's still in the in the
Okay.
list.
So, yeah,
just showing the explore explore function,
so it carries.
It carries the words.
It carries the first portion of the words
here,
so I can take all of these through to.
To the other modes and tools.
And how does it select what words it's
going to keep?
It's the first.
is the first set of words that will fit.
Hmm.
So, it will only take a maximum of 1 line.
You can.
You can tap and select counter.
You can, you can, yeah, so you can, um,
you can take one at a time,
Mhm.
so I just wanted to take difficult,
I can press difficult, explore.
Okay.
Ann.
And explore difficult.
So, it's just taking difficult there;
you can see,
Yeah.
but if I don't select anything,
it selects the first, um, first one.
And if I wanted difficult plus the next
word, so 2 words,
how do you how do you do that?
Yeah.
You can you can select multiple words
like this, it's not.
So, it's still a bit rubbish, but...
Yes, no.
Mm.
It's not that usable,
because we don't have the...
So yeah, it's taking me 3 or 10s,
but I can't get to it.
Yeah.
Some big handles would be.
But there's an 8.
There's an issue with a touch selection
because when you tap one word,
select the full word,
but when you tap and drag,
it moves down into character resolution
rather than keeping a word resolution.
So that's a fix that needs to be done to
be able to select full words.
multiple ones.
Yeah, OK.
Horizon in there.
Is in London.
Yeah.
Nothing's in there.
Yeah, so...
If I wanted to take all that text,
could I take all that text and explore or
We.
I.
not?
No, no, it will crop,
it will crop off the first,
it will crop off the last bit,
so it will take,
it will take what it can fit into the
text bar on the explore, yeah,
Into a single line.
onto a single line.
Okay.
No, you can take all.
But I selected everything I had on the
screen, and it brought everything over.
Okay.
Ann.
Okay, yeah, I'm wrong then. It was,
I think it's just if you don't select,
if you don't do a selection,
it just takes a single line.
Ed.
But as Peter said, if you take,
if you select all of it,
you can carry all of that over.
Mm.
Although that's not working for me, Peter.
Isn't.
Yeah.
Okay, let's try again.
I got full screen and text.
Yeah.
Selected it all.
Brought it all over, see the top line,
got everything.
Okay,
I think I think I know what might have
Ann.
happened actually.
Then I,
and I got have every all the words here
and more ones.
Beyond.
Right, then.
So it's...
Think what happened is.
B.
Okay.
Because I've got a pend on,
I think it split those two entries that I
scanned separately.
I.
Yeah, OK. Anyways, it's something I'll,
it's something.
I'll look into...
Have they fixed the left hand navigation
button? So back, home,
Ann.
do they work in all locations now?
Explore.
I haven't been able to find a place where
they don't work. Yeah.
Okay.
So yeah, they seem to be working.
As they should, much more.
Turn talking menu.
Yeah.
I love talking menu.
Ohh.
What about the bottom of the,
it seems pretty responsive with your
finger touching the screen now.
Does it generally feel better?
Bang.
Talking menu selected.
Heh.
The bottom of the screen was a bit worse
before. Again,
Okay.
Ed.
this is going back a couple of months.
Does it feel, does it feel okay now? So,
Yeah, and...
you know,
the place I really noticed it was when
you did the,
expanded navigation button and then you
were trying to press the explore or the
favourite or all those types of buttons.
Do you feel that they feel okay now?
There's still room for improvement. Yeah,
I think, yeah, it feels,
Okay.
it does feel better in some places, touch,
but there, yeah, it's still sometimes,
yeah, you have to get 2 taps or, yeah,
for those lower ones you sort of need to
hit the hit the button slightly,
slightly higher, so that's.
That's.
Okay.
That's yeah,
that's still still on the list, basically.
Yeah, we've got File Manager.
Functioning.
So we've got, yeah, saved words in here.
Actually checked the starred words. So,
easier I start landing earlier.
That's in here now against a red,
And what can you do with that landing?
Can you send it somewhere or is it just
a red star.
landing and you can't do anything with it?
You can't hear it or explore it or
whatever.
Yeah,
you can just you can just see it for now.
Yeah, OK.
And the idea is that you can access these
in Inspire as well.
I haven't checked the access from Inspire,
but you know it's safe against my student
account, basically.
You can.
Yeah, you are able to, but we've saved.
What does the what does the keyboard look
like?
Helps.
The keyboard,
the keyboard still looks the same.
Look.
That was an American spelling of
favourite, right?
Ohh.
And how successfully can you tap on that
keyboard?
I can.
Write your name, for instance.
I got the Peter on.
OK, as you can see with them.
Yeah, I'm not sure we can see that.
Sharmella, to answer your question,
I don't know,
but I'll make a note and I'll have a look
back.
We've got a we've got a pipeline item
task which is.
which is renaming,
like a branding slash renaming.
So, from...
Polishing, basically.
So yeah,
good support on the American spelling.
But that's the sort of thing.
Will.
Catching in that in that polishing.
But just from that little look there,
Theo, quick demo there. So.
Yeah.
Yeah,
truly essential things that need to be
working for the polishing, you know,
the startup screen,
Yeah.
but I imagine that's relatively simple,
I would hope. Text selection.
B.
You know, having that sort of nailed down,
that's really important, isn't it?
Yeah.
Second camera is really important.
Yeah.
UK voice is really important.
Touch improvements are really important.
You know, the more words,
I guess that's quite straightforward
anyway.
The QR logging is not quite as important
as some of the other things,
but because we could just remove it,
I guess.
But it would be nice to get that working.
But yeah,
just thinking about text selection,
second camera,
UK voice and touch improvements,
those four things there are really...
Yeah.
Are really biggies, aren't they? You know,
do we have do we have any idea of sort of
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
the time scales for these types of things?
Is it is it realistic that they're all
going to be fixed in the next 4 weeks,
six weeks?
Um...
Those 4.
I believe,
are all in the service project as
enhancements, and the...
They're not really enhancements though,
are they?
The UK.
In this terminology, it is.
I don't mind about that, but no.
Okay.
Yeah, ignoring semantics. Yeah, I, I,
yeah, I'd agree with you, Tony,
Yeah, yeah.
but we'd have different items called
different things, so yeah, that.
Mm.
All those four items that you just
described.
But the text selection for it,
just so I understand about enhancement,
Yeah.
to me an enhancement is something to make
it better in the future.
Mm.
Okay.
But the text selection, unless that works,
we're not letting anybody external see
the pen. So to me, that's polishing.
You know, and
Yeah, UK voice that.
But it's Toby, yeah, Toby, it's semantics.
If the ticket is completed and closed and
marked as done,
it's input as an enhancement in the
service project.
So it's not a change of something,
it's improving what's already on the pen
in this existing release.
So it has nothing it has nothing to do
with what we'll release publicly.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's just within the workflows of how
different things are defined depending on
the state of the previous original task.
Okay,
but do we think they're going to be fixed
in the next six weeks?
I would say yes.
Okay.
Yes, so yeah, they're on the list that,
yeah,
Mangesh has done his planning against,
you know, already the ones that are, yeah,
these aren't new ones that have cropped
up in the M11 review,
Okay.
so they're already in the,
they're already in the, yeah, backlog as,
you know, as...
Enhancements.
Yeah, fine.
Yeah.
Are you about to show us an activity?
Yeah, I can share your activity. I can't.
I thought I might have shown your
activity before,
but I can go through here.
So is the listener match,
listener match game.
So I've just heard the word juicy.
You can see we're using like similarly.
some similar,
some words with similarities in the way
that they're spelled,
got one XP for that behind.
Darkened.
Least, I'm gonna press the wrong one,
so you can see what happens. Uh,
if I went for light,
you can see I lost three seconds there,
stepped.
Thanks.
Patterns of the previous.
got repetition there easily.
This again.
I think that looks like a fun game.
Like that.
S.
Yeah, so it's quite rapid.
You get sort of instant feedback as you
go along.
Ann.
Shows you what you've won.
Okay.
At the end of it.
I can view all the answers here so I can
see what got wrong, what was right,
and then hit listen to it being spoken
again.
And if I continue takes you back to you,
I can I can start another one.
And there's a...
Each of the words that you saw there is
grouped into a reading difficulty score
that we've defined.
And there's a formula for how you
progress.
To take you to the next, the next stage,
and we are building in a, you know,
visibility of those levels into 360.
The.
As well, so...
Eventually.
And where do you start?
Uh, you start easy, so...
You.
We.
We mapped.
You might be in difficulty against ages.
So take the age of the student based on
their,
I can't remember if we used year or date
of birth, but we,
and then we went like a few, a few down.
So.
In most cases,
they're not just going to be getting...
They're not going to find it really hard
and find it frustrating.
They'll find it easy.
They'll win a few levels and then they'll
and then they'll move up and progress.
Or if they're really far behind,
they're not going to start and be like,
you know, it's not going to be way,
way off for them.
So it starts based on their age and then.
be good. Yeah, we've taken it down,
down a couple of pegs. And then you can,
you can, if you do really well,
then you can build up quite quickly to
get to the right sort of level that's
challenging, challenging for you.
And where can I can I see my XP anywhere
on the pen or do I have to wait and see
it in Inspire?
There's no at the moment you can see it
on your pen.
You have to see it in Inspire.
So eventually the idea is that it would
be in here.
Yeah.
So, yeah,
the only thing you've got is avatar.
Customization in here at the moment,
but yeah,
I will have the gamification elements.
In there.
Yeah,
just moving away from pen for a minute.
I'll just show you a couple of things,
couple of new things in.
In 360, yeah.
But before you go on, Theo,
that looks really quite good now,
apart from those things that I put in
bold in the chat.
Are there many other things on Theo's
list that you're not happy with?
Yeah.
Ed.
Ann.
Yeah, yeah, there's quite a few.
Ann.
And it might vary in.
nitpicky, you know,
what I'd say essentially usability for
you to nitpicky. So I'm just processing,
processing them at the moment.
But again, based on Theo, not India's say,
Theo say, how far off,
do you still realistically think that
these things are going to be done in the
Yeah.
Ed.
next four to six weeks?
Theo.
They're all fairly small, um,
so it doesn't, yeah,
definitely doesn't feel outside the
realms of possibility.
Um...
But I've got, yeah,
we've got a meeting with Mangesh tomorrow
to.
Talk through them and how you how they
how bending relates to plans.
Brighton.
Do you know which one of those that are
in the next?
There is another release coming up pretty
soon. So this one,
this release here is 3 to 4 weeks back.
But the next one is next,
I think they said this this week,
Yeah.
but let's say next week,
just hold on a sec,
do you know which of your comments are?
Already in the upcoming release,
and how many are beyond?
The next one we'll we'll get.
I haven't mapped them yet, so no,
I don't know at the moment. Yeah.
Okay, let's catch up tomorrow.
Yeah, I know, I know lots, yeah.
Those of them are already in service
projects in planning on the pre-pilot.
Yeah, the pre-pilot part.
Ann.
Another way of asking the same question
then,
Yeah.
how excited are you by the thought that
this may be ready in October?
How excited am I at the thought of this
being ready in October?
Yes, yeah, it's exciting. I don't know,
do I need to give you one at 1 to 10?
I think, um...
Well, it's like, you know, this is really,
I'm excited. It's going to be out there.
This is,
people are going to be experiencing it.
I'm really proud of it.
I think they're going to think it's
Ohh.
awesome.
Or are you still at the point where
you're thinking, well, okay,
I think this is a rush.
They're going to be disappointed.
Pointed, we're not gonna hit our targets.
Yeah,
that that's just that sort of emotional
feeling of, you know.
Okay, yeah.
There's there's a load of there's a load
of polish in this latest.
in the M11 release,
which is making it feel...
Like, I'll be, yeah,
I'm feeling much happier about going out.
Based, yeah, based on this M11 release,
yeah,
there's still there's still a few
fundamentals.
Those aren't new fundamentals,
they're stuff that's been in the service
projects in the pipeline for a while,
so they're part of the planning that,
yeah,
but the timeline and planning work that
my guess is.
The step back on, so...
There is.
So cautiously optimistic,
but not super excited yet.
Yeah.
Yeah,
I'll only I'll only be super excited once.
Once I, yeah,
once the things that have been in the
Is done.
backlog for a while have been...
Been resolved, and...
OK.
And yeah,
according to Mangesh is planning, yeah,
they should be.
Should be resolved.
Ann.
Listen, yeah, listen the dates given, so..
.
I'm feeling a lot happier in a lot of
areas.
But yeah, there's still,
there's still a few,
there's still a few fundamentals of which.
which are long-standing,
long-standing ones. There's nothing.
Something new, really, that's coming up.
That's that's concerning, so yeah,
in terms of new functionality.
OK.
Yeah, basically, there isn't much,
there's not much at all from the latest.
review that throws off the existing
planning.
That's probably the best way to describe
it.
Because that was that was one of the sort
of, you know, risk factors was that.
Based on the fact, we've got more,
you've got a new functionality, um,
and more reviews before, you know.
pending before Mangesh gave the, yeah,
did the planning and gave a time frame.
There's nothing from a recent review
which...
Which expands that big in a significant
way, so I'm...
I'm not too, I'm not,
I'm not the latest review hasn't scared
me by anything. Does that make sense?
Does that kind of reminds your question?
Yeah,
I'm going to go with your cautiously
optimistic,
but just not super excited yet.
I think I'll stick with my thoughts that
that's what you're where you're at.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think in all the years Theo has
been with us,
I've seen Theo super excited though.
I don't,
Funnily enough, Sharmella, I was about...
I wouldn't even know what super excited
for Theo would look like.
Yeah.
I, I was about to add that as well.
Yeah.
I was about to add,
I'm kind of looking forward to seeing
Yeah.
there in this sort of more animated. Yes,
we've done it in sort of stage.
The.
No.
But.
Yeah.
Yeah,
you were now at the at the school trials,
Ann.
and I think that's when I felt probably
excited.
and maybe shown and maybe shown it
slightly when the, you know,
Mm.
when the kids were working out.
what they needed from the pen.
Um, yeah, you know,
two kids are very different stages.
Yeah.
in the same year,
being able to use the pen for like to
meet their needs in the same in the same
session. That was like, yeah,
that was very cool. That was it.
A good, that was a good day.
I felt excited today.
Actually spit.
Yeah.
And just, yeah, not knocking down,
just trying to knock down barriers to
Hey.
make it as easier for kids as possible to
get to that point. This is the thing,
you know,
is the is the challenge we've got up to
pre-pilot, which is, you know,
all this polishing usability stuff.
Yeah, to make sure, you know,
to get to that point where they can
access those functions and they can
explore things and they're not going to
be getting frustrated with usability
stuff.
And performance stuff.
Yeah.
That's task, basically.
The pilots Quin have set up are there for
little little people or bigger little
OK.
Okay.
people that we know.
Primary, so.
Primaries are little people. OK.
Yeah.
And the primary.
Mm.
Yeah, so B.
Well, no, 10, 11.
Ten 11, yeah, believe, and...
So, so small, but not tiny.
Yeah.
Yeah.
Um...
Yes, a couple of things to show you in.
360.
So, it's like a...
Here, you can see I've got, you know,
my the ability to move between
organisations that I'm that I belong to
now,
Okay.
and we've got this little icon so you can
tell the difference,
Okay.
so I can swap between Springfield
Elementary here and Empowering Tech
Internal, which is what we set up to test.
best things.
I can move between between those
different Pens students and admins
between the both of them. So,
that's quite a significant structural
change. It doesn't look that massive,
but it's
It's an important, important one.
Ann.
What about the reports?
Have we got reports built by that third
party yet?
Payable.
Yes, so reports are functional. Yeah,
actually, so yeah,
thanks for reminding me.
I've got a few things,
so you can see here,
so here's this is the...
Embedded.
Power BI home page reporting.
We've got the two dashboards here.
There will also be a custom reports
button.
So custom reports under development at
the moment and there's polishing going on
of the dashboards at the moment.
So I'll show you.
Through the dashboards, this is all lie,
you know, real data.
This, this, yes,
in the back end at the moment,
you can see.
In terms of like visually.
This important,
this important thing that's needing this
important thing that's going going on,
so we've we've fed back on that and then
doing they're doing that.
That work,
which is to make it look more obvious,
that's right.
to make the information that's being
displayed more obvious,
what it is and a bit more engaging,
it's a little bit.
generic at the moment.
This is the pen dashboard. The dashboards,
in short, the dashboards are more about.
The top-level implementation.
Stats, so it's more about...
They're more for those people who are
interested in how.
How the ecosystem has been implemented
into and taken up,
so we've got stuff like most active years,
so out of the years of students that are
registered.
which years are the most active.
So it is of fine tuning a formula at the
moment which defines how a student,
how we define what active means and it's
a combination between, you know,
number of sessions, length of sessions,
number of actions within that session.
So we've got a formula that we're
fine-tuning and which defines that and we
define the averages from that.
Then we've got information here,
like which tools are most frequently used
by the students. So, for example,
is there...
We don't see anything there.
Is there data there?
No, you will, yeah, you will,
you will see that there.
So I think we have the top,
I think we have the top three here.
So it will say, you know,
it might be graphemes,
morphemes and syllables, for example.
Um, you know,
to give you sort of top-level view on.
What's the value of?
How are students getting the most use out
of these tools?
What's the value that they're getting
from interacting with it in terms of like?
Is it to do with, yeah,
breaking down of words, decoding,
and is it more to do with the enrichment
suite of tools that gives you a flavour
about?
How they're how they're being used?
So this is interesting sort of
implementation statistics,
then the custom dashboards being in
development at the moment,
which is more for the teachers.
So, like...
That enables you a much more granular,
a much more granular level of reporting
stuff like.
most commonly scanned words for this
group of students, you know.
Words listen to.
by these students in this amount of time
or by the student.
So it's more educator focused basically.
So the dashboards give the top level view
more relevant for those implement,
those interested in how the product's
been implemented.
And then the custom reporting is
Is more about educational insights into
different students, and...
Really?
Yeah, we're in the purse of...
Ann.
Yeah,
the developing the UIs to be implemented
in here, and...
Exactly which KPIs are included in that.
Um,
based on based on the amount of data that
we're collecting in in the back end.
So, yeah, it doesn't, it's not looking,
it's not looking that great at the moment,
but it's functioning, and there's there's.
..
Yeah,
polishing work that's going on at moment
to make the.
Information more visible, more obvious,
and more engaged.
And we're certain that we're capturing
all the information at the moment.
So we're capturing what mode they're in,
how long they're in there, what, you know,
the length of time, you know, who it is,
you know, the words they're scanning,
Yeah.
they're listing, the button. You know,
we are capturing all that information of
interaction on a pen and writing it into
the database.
Yes.
Yes, there we are.
But.
Yeah, so that's reporting.
I'll just cheque.
I don't think I had anything else.
On 360.
Yeah.
Yeah, nothing else on 360, so.
Yeah, to summarise.
Has anything happened on Inspire?
Nothing recently on Inspire I can report
on. I need to complete the.
I need to, I need to complete the review.
Last time I last time I checked in on
Inspire,
there was if there was a few things not
not mapping and a few bugs,
so I need to cheque in.
I need to cheque in on that before I can,
yeah,
before I can really comment on on states
of.
Of inspire.
Um...
And then the last thing, words database,
which is...
Yeah, with.
We generated 3K, yeah, 3K words.
We've just re...
Reminders how much that cost.
Find my spreadsheet.
And did it go as well when you went up
from up to 3000 words? Did it?
Was it easy?
Was it just a case of saying 3000 and
then it did it?
B.
Yeah, generation-wise, there's no...
No different, it takes, yeah,
it takes more time.
So it costs 6000 US dollars, is that?
Intensive.
Ohh, to get to 20K. OK.
P.
Yeah.
So, yeah, 3K was around...
Fifteen 100.
Yeah, around less, yeah,
less is less than 1500.
It was 3K, not 5K.
But the new,
the new model we just generated across.
is about 10%.
Of that.
So the way that we're conducting the test.
The test that went,
we're reviewing the cheaper model.
and defining which LOCs we can use are
suitable.
The...
you know,
give us the quality that we need.
Against each LOC.
So what we'll end up with is it.
For us, you know,
somewhere in between for MVP,
somewhere in between 6K dollars and $500.
Depending on sort of complexity, so...
It's quite a big difference, isn't it?
Massive difference, yeah, massive.
Yeah.
And yeah,
it makes a huge difference as we scale.
Um, you know,
you start to get full dictionary, yeah,
Back there.
makes makes a huge, a huge difference, so.
..
Okay.
Yeah, with.
Oh.
Starting.
The reviews.
of the 3K based on the cheaper LLM.
And then, if we need, if we need to,
then we can refer back to this first.
Okay.
And how did you get on with the safety
features? Let's say, call it that.
Were you happy with what what the what
you've done?
There's, yeah, 3 levels of safeguards.
Part of the review of what's going on
here will tell us how well,
tell us how well we've done,
because part of what we're reviewing for
the 3K, you know,
based on this new LLM and the older LLM
that we've
Been working with part of that is about.
you know, by the safety of those words,
of the content generated.
The first,
the first level is tagging offensive
words and sensitive words. You know,
our current strategy is not to generate
anything against the sensitive,
against the offensive words, so we've...
Got a list of words that we we tagged
from our, you know,
hundreds of thousands of words,
and now we provide you list.
So,
we can we can revisit them when we know.
how to handle them,
basically what we should do with them
from an educational ethical point of view.
So, that's the first bit that that worked,
that worked.
Quite well,
it was a little overzealous in some
places,
which I spoke about in a previous call,
like flagging Assassin,
'cause there's a couple of ***** in
Assassin, so it was a little,
it was a little overzealous.
Then into, and then the next, yeah,
the next safeguard is in terms of the...
generation.
So the LLMs have their own built-in
content generation safeguards.
So, that's the next one,
and then the next one after that is us
checking the content,
checking samples of the content that's
been generated. So,
in our next set of reviews, you know,
we've got words which...
And...
We've got words.
that have like a, you know,
a secondary meaning for something that
could be offensive.
So we're reviewing them. For example,
something like bulls, right?
So creating examples and definitions
against against a word like bulls.
Yeah, we're checking whether it's...
Generated a meaning.
generated the meaning,
which could be described as, you know,
like crude or offensive.
And then if it has,
How does that? How does that?
What the exact,
how sensitivity has it has it done that?
Does it say something like a word used to
describe an anatomical part?
And then,
and then the examples that come from that
ExCo, which is,
which is one of the risky areas,
the examples are one of the risk areas.
So.
Yeah, the first layer is working,
working quite well,
is a little over overzealous.
And we're reviewing the next two.
layers of safeguards in our latest review
by pulling out the words, you know,
that may have the double meanings.
And we get, we've got them,
we've got sample lists for each of those,
each of those defined.
Ann.
So yeah,
first level is working well and to answer
your question, yeah,
the first level is working well and the
next two layers are under review.
Basically what we've got, we've got
We've got Jacks in place.
So,
I can I can update you once we've once
you've gone through it through that that
process and show you what that looks like.
Stuff. Sorry, another question for me,
sort of going off sort of where you're at,
Mhm.
but what about the planning for the next
stage?
you know,
what comes after this is all agreed.
I know we've had a couple of meetings and
we've cancelled them or delayed them
because you guys weren't ready.
But are we getting closer to being able
Yeah.
to actually start talking about
priorities for after launch?
We don't want there to be a lag.
Mm.
between us finishing this load of work
and starting the next load of work,
Boome.
I guess, do we?
Ann.
Okay.
I can say a bit of that.
I think that up until year end,
I think we should focus on things that we
have intentionally left behind a bit.
We have small things that we've said,
okay, let's wait and let's wait.
We'll spend the first few months,
focus on that and get that in.
And then beyond that,
So, oh.
in parallel with that being done,
I think we should consider what the next
level really is, the priorities,
where we want to go,
if we want to improve or enhance even
further about the things we already have,
or if we want to add another layer on.
onto it.
Things like adding more activities is
definitely in my book.
Having one single doesn't really cut it
Mm.
very far. We need to think about that.
And then I would probably look into
adding more valuable
Old teachers for teachers.
Yep.
Support them in any generation of
worksheets or some whatever makes sense
Yeah, I agree.
there, but within that within that area,
I think we can getting.
So,
you're not worried that you're not
Okay.
worried people are gonna run out of
things to do before we set the these next
Boome.
tasks, the this next priorities though.
Okay.
No,
I think we can keep basically everyone
busy with things we already have in the
backlog and we can basically just pick
things and move forward there and make
sure that everyone has across the
functions, they have things to do.
And in parallel, we try to have a few
Brainstorming sessions and setting the
direction for.
for the next larger initiative of change.
Because I want, I would want us not to.
Continue spoon feeding feature by feature,
small things at the at each time,
but keeping them busy for a while, post.
start a pilot,
but then having a larger initiative that
will be the next.
iteration where everyone basically has
something to do for a few months.
And if it doesn't keep everyone busy,
then we can have some side tasks that we
want to push through else.
But I want to take a larger grip.
Kind of moving it.
a window objective further and not just
by something that can spin around in two
to four weeks.
Okay.
Hmm.
But soon enough, soon enough,
we need to have a session where we sit
down and do that.
Just that Theo has been up over his head
for a while now,
and will be for a couple of weeks more,
I guess.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, we, we've got the, yeah,
we've got the...
The plan of how to...
Hard to process, yeah,
I just haven't been able to give it the
Yeah.
time to try to process it and, you know,
effectively create.
Create those.
buckets for new features and beyond
immediate polishing.
OK.
And I think we all want to get the
product launch, you know,
at this minimum level to a very high
standard so that people start using it
Mm.
and thinking this is cool straight away.
And from what we've seen,
I think as long as even this minimum
functionality that we've got is done to a
Okay.
cool, is done to a high standard,
I think people will think it's a cool
product moving it on.
But yeah,
I think we probably all equally want to
start seeing some more features being
developed and added on progressively
The.
month after month after month just so
that we can see it moving. So yeah,
Mm.
but first things first,
let's launch product to high quality with
what we've got there at the moment.
So, yeah, OK.
Yeah.
Ann.
Yeah, I just got the,
I did just get the QR code log in to work
second time.
I wasn't really able to show you,
but yeah, yeah,
just an example of a little bit of
glitchiness, bit of bugginess to get to.
Yeah,
some of these newer features feeling more
robust.
Cool.
Okay.
Yeah, nothing else, nothing else for me.
Right. Nothing else. We're at Q&A.
All good.
It's all looking really good Theo,
well done.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's all looking really,
really good.
Thanks.
Yeah.
I agree.
Gradually, gradually coming together.
Yeah, we will see Theo smile.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks, Theo.
One day, maybe.
Ugh.
But there's big progress there on many
fronts.
Yeah.
Yeah.
Mm.
Brilliant.
Rights.
Cool. Thanks, everyone. Thanks, Theo.
Bye bye.
Cool. Okay. Thanks everyone.
Thanks everyone. Bye bye. Bye.
Thanks, everyone.
Thanks a lot, Theo. Thanks. Bye, bye.
Thanks, Theo. Bye. Cheers. Bye.